be unmuted.
Okay, perfect. All right, let's begin.
Welcome everyone. Uh this is uh we're
doing a master class today. So, I'm
going to be going over how uh I've been
selling digital products
um specifically on X organically lately.
So, you know, I've generated over $15
million at 22. So, I'm going to be
showing you how. So, how do I go to the
next? There we go. Okay. So today I'm
going to be going over a few things. So
first I'm going to be going over my uh
biography or story. Uh showing you like
who I'm about because a lot of you guys
have been asking for that. Um and then
some exercises to help you d uh attain
your dream future. And then basically a
lot of the technical stuff that I
promised. of how to get views on X, how
to create digital products with AI. Um,
and there are many different uh ways
that you can go about this. So, I'll be
explaining to you everything uh step by
step. So, there are a lot of steps um
you know each step is small and there
are a lot of pictures that I've attached
so that you can see exactly how it works
uh in detail. And then at the very end
there is a special opportunity for you
to join me and my team um and also
giveaways. So uh the more uh time we
spend on this master class basically the
more value you're going to get and uh
it's going to be more important towards
the end. So um in the beginning it will
just be a few exercises my in my story
and then later on uh we'll be going over
the technical details basically what you
guys came here for. All right. So a lot
of the stuff I basically share um it in
my uh private group for my mentorship
students. Um but you know I'll be
sharing with you guys uh what I teach
them uh to you guys here. So who is this
master class for? So it's basically for
anyone or everyone uh for beginners, for
those who are already you know making
lots of money um you know helping you to
scale to six figures per month or seven
figures per month or even if you're
unsure or just want to learn.
So for those who don't know me uh why
you should listen to me when there are
millions of other people who are trying
to give business advice, right? So I'm
going to share some of my stats. So I
have more than 50 X accounts uh and
we're getting millions of views
regularly every week. So um these X
accounts are in variety of different
topics uh
like ecom AI sales YouTube sweeps uh
stuff like that. So as long as if it's
in business and we're educating people,
teaching people, helping them grow, um
you know that's what we have. And then
most of these accounts are faceless. So
as you know my account uh I show my
face. Um there's one or two others that
show their face but all these all the
rest of the accounts are completely
faceless. So if you're doing this
business you don't need to show your
face. So you know in the analytic
section we're getting millions of views
regularly. All right.
Okay.
So basically breaking down the funnel uh
in easy words. So first we're creating
uh posts right we're creating hundreds
or thousands of posts across many
different accounts right and then uh
this is basically the steps that the
audience the viewers go through uh so
that they become clients and buy. So
basically they will um go through the
posts and they'll be curious to learn
more right they'll go through more posts
they'll go through uh the freebies that
we send or other materials that we have
for maybe telegram or discord
communities um they'll go through them
and then uh they'll be interested to
learn more
>> [snorts]
>> um the point for us is to give as much
value as possible so that they can learn
and we can earn their trust and then you
want to to uh you know you want to have
some sort of way to uh capture them. So
you know maybe like 1 to 3% or 5% of
these people will end up wanting more
and buy something. So you know that
could be an ebook or that could be a
course or coaching. So for for if it's
like a smaller amount of payment uh like
30 bucks or 500 bucks then it makes
sense to do a checkout link. But if it's
a lot more expensive, like thousands of
dollars or 20K, then it makes sense to
do a text or call, have a closer, and uh
uh since they're paying a lot and then,
you know, of course, getting sales and
then each account is making anywhere
from four to six figures in sales uh per
month. So that's essentially how it
works on the on the big scale.
All right. Um [clears throat]
so yeah these are some of my analytics
or uh sales dashboards. So uh in the
past four weeks you can see that um you
know we've done more than 500k and then
in the past 6 months we've done uh 2.4.
For those who are saying that it's fake
or you know it's edited um you can go to
my Twitter or YouTube or Instagram or
you know I have videos in a lot of
places refreshing and doing all that
sort of stuff. So, um, you know, I just
didn't include it there here because I
didn't know how to include videos, but,
um, these are my sales.
All right. Um, and you know, you know
that I had to include it in here. Uh,
basically the cars. Uh, so this is a
Lamborghini Huracan Evo. I'm fortunate
enough to have to be able to drive
these. Uh, this Ferrari actually, uh, I
haven't boughten yet. So, uh, this is
rented. So, maybe like I would rent for
like a few weeks at a time or like a
month at a time. Um, so like all the
other cars besides this black one, um,
is rented. So, you know, the Ferrari,
the Urus, the red one, the black one,
uh, those are all rented besides this
one on the left. Um, you know, I just
had to put it in there. Uh, just to
flex. Um, you know, besides the monetary
stuff, basically preparing to have a new
family soon. Uh, maybe be a dad, who
knows? Um, also a son of God. So, you
know, this is basically how I identify
myself. It's like, you know, before all
these, uh, you know, things that I've
accomplished, um, I put myself as, you
know, a family member and also the son
of God. So, you know, I'm trying to
follow God. Um, doing my best to
basically follow, um, I'm very I'm a
very sinful and terrible person, but,
you know, it's basically my
responsibility to keep improving and
also to help other people to come to God
as well. So, you know, that's who I am.
And then now, uh, because a lot of you
guys have been asking me, here's a quick
story about myself. It'll take like
probably 5 minutes. So, you know, I was
born in Utah. Um,
uh, Japanese roots. Um, grew up in the
East Coast, basically. Did a lot of
swimming in piano. Uh, that's me with
Phelps. Um,
you know, the reason why I'm giving you
my story is just because, um, you know,
I hope that, uh, maybe I just want to
show you that I'm not like anything
anyone who's like extraord like
extraordinarily special. um and show you
like um like how I did it to give you
more context and maybe you can relate
with me. So you know uh college was
basically the time uh where things
started to change. You know I had quit
these things that I had been doing
before. Um came here to LA where I'm
right now. Um you know I'm trying to
figure out my life. I have no money and
basically I almost died in an accident.
I was skateboarding and I almost die. Um
so this was you know the point of my
life where I'm trying to figure out uh
what my life is, what to do and um yeah
so basically I was starting to get
worried right um you know after college
I'd work a job probably my boss would
tell me what to do um control my entire
life I could get fired at any time would
I be able to support my family you know
uh am I going to slave under him for the
rest of my life and also um
you because I have all this all these
fears. I tried um so many different
businesses, right? I'm watching how to
make money online YouTube videos um and
I just try so many different businesses
and I fail all of them. All right. So,
uh during college, I take one semester
off. So, that means like one for one of
the six months that I had, I basically
stopped going to school. Um and I went
all in on business basically. So, um,
you know, 12 12 hours per day to figure
it out. Um, the goal, uh, by the end of
the six months was to get to 10K per
month, and I had no idea how I was going
to do that. And it felt like I was
climbing a mountain basically like I was
at the very bottom. And the top I
imagined that I would attain it, but
then I realized that, oh wow, 10K feels
incredibly far, infinitely far, even if
I'm like, you know, climbing so much. So
at that time I thought it was completely
impossible.
Um you know I had zero success. Um you
know these images I basically took from
my own Instagram account. So you know I
hope these um images help kind of
describe everything. Um
so you know I'm doing all these sort of
stuff. Uh I have zero success and then
as last attempt I try selling software
on LinkedIn basically.
All right. And then, you know, finally,
uh, this one post after spending like,
you know, months and months on business,
like it finally gets views. Um,
you know, this was the first $10 sale
I've ever gotten. The first ever sale
I've gotten. Um, you know, thanks to
Emma. Basically, she Venmoed me 10 bucks
for the software. Uh, October 202
something. Um, probably like three years
ago. October 24. Um, so this was the
first ever sale I've gotten. Basically,
I was in the college dining hall. You
know, even though I wasn't enrolled in
classes, I was in the dining hall. Um,
and I was so happy. I called my parents
and my friends and I was smiling for
probably two or three hours.
So, you know, I started doing LinkedIn
basically created like so many different
profiles. Um, so these are fake profiles
that I made and I'm making these kinds
of posts. I'm making like 100k to 3
million views per post. So, you know,
we're absolutely going viral. We're
promoting a software and then I'm doing
six figure months. And so, it was a huge
leap from there. And then all these
accounts get banned. Um, you know,
that's the one thing about LinkedIn is
that it's so easy to get banned. Um,
so, you know, all this stuff, all this
stuff basically came to zero.
All right. So that's basically why I
started doing X is because, you know,
LinkedIn sucks. Uh it's so easy to get
banned. So I was looking for, you know,
platform where I could survive long
term. And the nice thing about X is just
that you don't get banned. Like you
could do anything and it's like very
secure, very stable. You can survive
there forever. Okay. So um for the first
two or three months, I was probably
making 10 posts, more than 10 posts per
day every single day and I was getting
zero views, right? And then after maybe
like two or three months, I get my first
viral post. So at that point, I've
already made hundreds and hundreds of
posts, all getting zero views. And then
finally, I get one, my first viral post.
And of course, like up until that point,
I'm making zero. But then the first post
gets, you know, I'm basically selling an
ebook and I make five figures from that.
All right. Um, so I just want to go over
some disclaimers. one, I wanted to, you
know, basically make it clear that I
didn't get any financial help from
anyone. Like, I could ask my parents for
money, but I just didn't want to. Like,
that was the last thing I would ever do.
I I felt like I would rather die trying
to figure out business than asking for
help. Um, two is that I didn't know any
businesses before, you know, all this
stuff. You know, I was just searching up
how to make money online, like searching
that on like YouTube, basically. Uh,
three is, you know, I'm not very I'm not
that smart. I failed lots of exams and
finals in college in school. Um,
and four, I wanted to, you know, let you
guys know that I'm not lucky at all.
I've tried so many different businesses.
I've failed more than eight of them. And
so, uh, I have basically a long streak
of being super unlucky. Um, yeah. So, if
I'm not special, then why did I succeed?
And the answer is because uh I found the
blueprint that works. So um you know I
found the method um the exact blueprint
um you know it's similar to having a
treasure map. Basically if you have that
map if you have the blueprint of how to
build you know uh some furniture if you
have like a like a manual of how to
build a Lego set then you know you can
make it work. You just need to find that
blueprint.
All right. So, back in that time when I
was spending like 12 hours per day, um
you know, I did realize that it was
completely inefficient. It was like
trying to fi fill a bucket of water with
a spoon. Like that's analogy that I use.
It was so inefficient. And looking back,
I realized that I could instead just
spend like 30 minutes or an hour per day
and just do the and you know, do even
more than I did back then. You know, get
even better results. So, this is
basically what I'm going to teach you
guys is, you know, not to do uh all the
mistakes that I made. Um but, you know,
show you guys basically what I learned
and what I'm doing now. That's most
efficient.
All right. So, um what I do is actually
pretty simple. So, you know, as you
know, basically selling digital products
on X across many many different
accounts. So, you have to uh use these
four things in order to succeed. So
one is you have to use AI. You know now
if you're not using AI then you're uh
getting behind. You're being left
behind. Um two you need to learn how to
crack the algorithm. Basically um you
know there are unwritten rules on X of
how to get views and not only how to get
views but how to get the right views.
You know, I was working with a Twitter
page that was getting five million views
per day, but we weren't making any sales
because the quality of the people were
so low versus, you know, I have accounts
that are getting only a thousand views
per day. And because the quality is so
high, you know, basically all the
followers are experienced entrepreneurs.
So, you know, we're making so much.
We're making um you know, more than
$20,000 per month from that page alone.
So you know basically cracking the
algorith algorithm so that you get lots
of views and target the right people you
know that's very important and you need
to learn how to do that. Um you know all
the stuff I'll be explaining to you uh
as we go along in the webinar. Um you
know number three is you need help from
retweets from other big accounts. So,
you know, for example, if you're making
a brand new post, if you get retweets
boost from me and, you know, all my big
accounts, that's going to increase the
likelihood of you going viral um by
manifold, right? And then there are a
lot of templates that you can use. So
you've probably noticed by now that
there are a lot of posts on X uh that
are you know very similar formats, same
templates, same styles and you know the
reason why uh people keep making those
posts is because it works every single
time. So once you know these templates
um and all this then you know basically
it's very simple. It's very easy. Um I
wouldn't say it's easy but you know um
it makes a lot of sense. It's very
simple. All right. And I'll be giving
you guys lots of templates, all the
templates that I have later on. Um, and
also sharing with you how to crack the
algorithm and how it works. All right?
And also how to use AI.
So, um, you know how I was spending a
lot of time when I was starting out
business like two or three years ago,
but now once you do all of this, right,
you can boil it down to spending just 7
to 10 hours per week working on this
business to become successful.
All right. Um, so you know, I've
basically figured out the algorithm. Um,
gotten millions of views, generated
millions in sales, and I figured out how
it works. So, I'll be teaching you guys
this. All right. So,
now that we're done with the story and
the basic overview, I want to go over a
simple exercise. So, to help you guys,
um, I want you guys to imagine your life
in one year from now. Exactly one year
from now. So 2027 in February, uh what's
what's today's date? 19. All right. If
you could literally achieve anything.
So I want you to basically uh have the
answers very clear in your mind or write
it down. So what number will you see on
your monthly sales dashboard? Right? How
much will he be making online with
online business? So think of an answer,
right? How much do you want to be
making? Is it 30K per month? Do you want
to make 50K per month? So, just write
that down. All right. Two is where
you're living, right? Are you living uh
where you are right now? Or are you
going to be living somewhere better? Are
you going to be living um in a house
next to the ocean in what country?
Or are you going to be living uh with
some friends who are entrepreneurs who
are at the same level as you?
All right. Three. I want you to imagine
uh who are you surrounded by? Um
are you surrounded by other highle
entrepreneurs?
Um are you well connected with a lot of
them? Um do you have people around you
that respect you
and how are they treating you? And the
four is what does your schedule look
like?
This is all by the way, you know, if
hypothetically you could achieve
anything then what what would your
answers be here? Would your schedule be
completely empty? Would you be working
from 4:00 a.m. to, you know, 10:00 a.m.
and then for the rest of the day, um,
you can do whatever you want. Maybe
you're free location-wise, right? Maybe
you have enough time to really uh spend
time with your family, take care of your
family. So what does your schedule look
like? So I want you to have these goals
very clear in your mind or written on
paper and we'll come back to this later.
All right. All right. So now that we
have gotten all that out of the way, um
I want to go over the basic details. So
some of you guys joining this master
class, you guys are going to be
completely new. So I'm going to go over
everything from A to Z. So just to
remind [clears throat] you guys, uh
digital product is anything that's
non-physical. So basically like stuff
that you can't touch, right? Maybe like
a ebook, course, coachings, communities,
softwares, um anything that can be
delivered uh from your computer or your
phone, like anything that's digital
basically. And you can sell it unlimited
number of times, right? It doesn't cost
it barely costs anything to create it or
to sell it. You can just copy
infinitely.
You know this market is huge. Uh people
underestimate the market of digital
products but it's $2.5 trillion market.
You know this is basically stat from
WAP. Um and it keeps growing. you know
it's growing much faster than uh you
know many other different industries
and the e-learning market you know which
is a subset you know within digital
products it's a 430 billion market so uh
just for clarity e-learning is a subset
within this 2.5 trillion market so all
the all e-learning uh products are
digital products but not all digital
products are e-learning so that is
basically
the difference there and you know if you
look at this chart from market US the
market cap keeps increasing um I don't
know if that's the right word but the
market keeps increasing so every four
years or so it um basically doubles
right right now it's 2026 430
uh billion dollars in 2020 no 2030 it's
going to be 169 so you can see basically
that it's doubling every four
So, you know, if for example, you're
making uh you know, $10,000 per month
right now, then it would make sense to,
you know, be making $20,000 per month
given that nothing changes, right? So,
if you look if you look at things for
the long-term perspective, then, you
know, it makes a lot of sense to go in
this. It's a huge uh it's a very good
investment compared to other industries
that are you know stagnant getting more
saturated and decreasing. All right. So
this is very good place to be. All
right. So who is selling digital
products in e-learning? Uh basically
info products.
Um I want to show you guys that
basically everyone's everyone is
selling. So, you know, if you take a
look at um like presidents, world
leaders like Obama, um you know, he made
$65 million basically writing uh a book,
right?
That technically is like e-learning. Um
it's like it's an info product.
Universities are making it a crapload of
money, right? Every university is making
lots of money. Um I wouldn't say every,
but you know, many of them are. my
university. This is my uh university by
the way. It's a USC here in LA. Um you
know this I I was living here and
basically these buildings this block
called the village cost $700 million to
to build. So it's almost a billion. You
can see how nice it is and how much
money they have. Like they're making5
billion dollars per year. I mean, it's
it's mainly like due to us students
basically paying a crapload of money. I
think it's like $80,000 per year per
student now. So, you know, they're
making a lot of money. They're selling
courses, right? They're selling courses,
they're selling um digital products
online.
Uh this is basically the final boss of,
you know, digital products are selling
courses. By the way, um big companies,
uh media companies, newsletter
companies, uh are selling digital
products. So, they're making 10 billion
per year, 12 billion per year. And then,
you know, the real question is who isn't
selling digital products? You have all
these celebrities, influencers, people
with followers on Instagram, YouTube,
wherever, they're all selling digital
products. Like, who isn't selling one,
right? Maybe they have a course, maybe
they have like a newsletter, uh maybe um
and maybe like they're just making money
through their social media itself. Like
that's a digital product too, right? So
everyone is making money selling digital
products. And the only person who isn't
is probably you that's watching, right?
All these big people that are successful
are selling digital products. So it
doesn't make any sense for you to not
to. All right. So now we're going to go
into the next part of the master class
which is POV. You become my student. So
um like imagine you're my son, right?
You're my son and uh if you're my son, I
want to do whatever it takes to make you
s make you become successful ASAP,
right? I'm going to tell you what to do
uh how to grow business like starting
from like age of like three or
something, right? So this is what I
would do the path the step-by-step
process that uh you would um go on if
you're my student or my son or you know
whoever I want to teach. So this is how
we're going to do. Um
first I have a discord channel basically
where I have a community. I have a lot
of resources. I have uh 52 course
modules. So you know this is in the
format of videos, documents, guides
basically a place where you can learn
everything. So everything that I've
learned within this business um
like all the knowledge I have in my head
I put it into these 52 course modules. I
keep updating it every week so that it
it keeps increasing. Um and I'll give
you guys access. Um so you know these
are some of the modules. I have so many
in there. Um
so if you're starting out this business
basically step one for you would be to
acquire an old X account. And the reason
why is because um you want to warm up
your your account. Uh if it's fresh new
then X is going to think that's
suspicious. So, um, you know, again, we
want to use X as the main marketing
platform.
All right. And then you want to get a
blue check mark. Um, set up your
profile. The blue check mark getting
verified costs $8 per month. It's
basically zero. Um, and then the reason
why you want to do X compared to, you
know, why not do it on YouTube or Tik
Tok or Instagram or, you know, do paid
ads.
>> [snorts]
>> So this is all organic and there are few
reasons why X is the number one place to
do marketing. So one is that you know um
it's only text right it's only text you
don't have to create videos it takes
hours just to film edit videos uh for
YouTube Instagram Tik Tok for just one
video right and that takes hours to do
and what if it doesn't you know get
views uh versus X you can create
hundreds of posts within just a few
minutes especially using AI and even if
only a small fraction of those posts
goes viral. Um, you know, you're getting
lots of views. Basically, it's hyper
efficient. So, that's why it's like 30
times or maybe even more faster and
easier. Uh, it's just hyper efficient.
Number two is that the quality of leads
are a lot higher on Twitter, right?
Instagram and Tik Tok, those like those
are videos like people just watch brain
rot videos, right? That's 99% of the
people versus X, people are reading.
people are reading like educational
stuff. People in X are intelligent. Uh
they're wiser. They're um more
successful. They're wealthier. Um
they're just like high quality people um
compared to like Tik Tok and Instagram.
So, you know, on X because people are
wealthy, a lot of the followers tend to
be entrepreneurs already or, you know,
they work a really nice 9 toive job. So,
basically, high quality leads. Uh
they're very ambitious. They're very
likely to take action. they're very
likely to buy from you um and very
likely to pay a lot too uh per client.
So even if you're only getting like a
few thousand views, uh chances are
you're going to be making so much more
with just a few thousand views on X
compared to getting millions of views in
front of, you know, brain rod people on
Tik Tok or these video platforms
basically. And also another thing is
that you can just autodm people. So,
whenever someone likes or comments on
your post on X, you can automate your
DMs. You can send everyone like a
checkout link if you wanted to. You
could send them like a freebie or send
whatever you want. So, let's for example
like if you get 400 or 500 comments on a
post on one post, then you can autodm.
You can set up a DM feature that
automatically and instantly DMs them
like everyone
like a checkout link to a course or
something like that. Maybe like one or
two% of people buy, right? It's
basically automated. Uh so auto DMs are
huge. All right. You can use AI to
basically generate these posts uh within
a few seconds or minutes and you can use
AI to uh create the products as well and
to set up the funnels uh versus you know
with videos on Instagram, Tik Tok, um
YouTube, it's a lot harder to do. And
you know the goal eventually is to
automate your business, right? You don't
want to be working all the time. Um if
you're smart, you want to build systems.
you want to build an engine just like
how you know Elon Musk or Jeff Bezos
they're not working on everything in the
business they barely do anything what
like all they do is just like give
instructions and just like they have
like a vision um and they tell um
they're the people under them like what
the vision is and what to do maybe like
a few decisions per day like hyper um
high level uh high lever decisions right
um so that's where you want to be you
want to be the owner of this. You want
to basically um not do all these tedious
work but you know to be um a visionary.
You want to be the guy who is um you
know taking control of all this owning
it without doing much of the work. And
so um this is all organic mean meaning
that you don't have to pay anything to
you know get views. Um
so you know that's why the investment
into this business is so little. Um you
know just c you can just get started
with like with zero honestly you can
just open X start making posts but my
recommendation is for you to um get
Tweet Hunter and get premium. So that
costs $38 per month. Um besides that
there is like no investment to get
started. All right. So that is why it's
so um nice.
All right. So step three is you want to
pick a topic or niche. You know, you
want to pick something um because
obviously if you're posting about
everything all the time, then um it's
going to be confusing. You need to be
consistent. So you need to pick one
thing. All right.
Okay. So um pick a niche like AI, ecom,
YouTube. As long as it is business
related, it's fine. Um, you can even
pick like health relationships or any
other niche as long as um, you know,
you're providing lots of value.
All right, Q&A.
All right, so um, how do I close this?
All right, so number four, I want you
guys to understand the purpose of all
this. Um, you know, it's nice to get
lots of views and make lots of money,
but um, you know, the primary goal is
really to make posts that will genuinely
help other people like learn, grow, you
want to help other people. Uh, that way
that you know, you're giving out value
to the world and you're benefiting
others. So, you should be focusing on
that as number one.
All right. Um, step five, you want to
find a partner who is successful.
So, for example, let's say an
entrepreneur named Ben. He's selling AI
to big companies, right? And he's making
millions of dollars per year. You want
to partner with him. And you know,
you're probably thinking, "How can I
possibly partner with anyone? You know,
I don't know anyone like that." And if
that's the case, don't worry. I have so
many um you know, friends. I have a huge
network of people uh easily over 300
very successful entrepreneur friends
friends that you can partner with. All
right. Uh so you know if you just
message me then I'll connect you guys.
All right.
Okay. So why do you need a partner?
The reason why I would recommend for you
to find a partner is because uh like
chances are you're not successful. You
don't have experience, right? And if
that's the case, that's very difficult.
Like if you're trying to post about AI,
for example, like look at the guy on the
left. Like if that's you, you don't have
real experience. You don't have real
background, then you know, no one's
going to listen to you. You're not going
to be confident. But the partner, the
guy who's actually successful with AI,
he's going to be confident. he's going
to have all these stories, these stats,
um, and he's going to get a huge
audience and lots of views, right? But
the problem is that he's already busy
with his company, his business. So, he
has no time to make posts. So, that's
where you're going to come in is you're
going to make posts for him, right? So,
you're going to join him. You're going
to join your partner and basically post
together. So, he gives you the knowledge
and experience, but he doesn't have any
time to post, right? But you have all
the time to do that. So that you will
make the post, you'll set up the funnels
and all the stuff. So you know basically
you guys are um contributing in these
different ways. All right. So you want
to divide up the work. Again, you know,
Ben is experienced. He's successful with
this business, but um he doesn't have
the time to make posts or to, you know,
uh build these funnels, but you do. So
you're going to create these posts on
behalf uh on his behalf to generate
views.
Um it's getting kind of dark. So let me
All right. So he gives you the knowledge
and the authority. He shares all of that
with you. Um so that you know you can
learn from him. And so once you have
that then you can start making posts.
All right. So let's say Ben he is the AI
millionaire guy. uh he has no time but
he gives you like basically rundown of
how his business works right he's making
money selling uh AI to businesses so he
gives you like a 30page ebook basically
showing you exactly how his business
works so you go through all of it you
basically absorb everything you need to
know about his business right so
um you receive it and you read it
yeah this is the example of the ebook on
the right and then you start making
posts. So again, you know your partner
Ben, he's very busy. He has no time to
make posts. He has no time to do any of
this work because he's already doing his
own business, but you have his knowledge
and his experience now. So uh you're
going to start uh making posts on his
behalf. So you start making lots of
posts
and you want to use cloud or some AI to
generate these tweets. you know, you
want to create these um but you know,
chances are it's going to take a lot of
time and also it's going to be difficult
to, you know, figure out what kind of
posts get lots of views. So, um and also
you want to, you know, find viral posts
on X, um you know, posts that are
already going viral basically that you
want to copy.
So, you feed both of those into Claude.
For example, Claude, for those of you
that don't know, Claude is similar to
ChateBT or Gemini. Uh, so basically like
um Ben's ebook from earlier, you feed it
to Claude and also you, let's say you
scrape 50, you know, very um popular
viral tweets that he found um and then
you basically feed both of them into
Claude. So, you know, you give context
and then you're like, "Okay, so based
off these tweets, uh, try to figure out
why they went viral." So, learn from the
style, the format, the template of these
viral tweets, and the AI will basically,
uh, reverse engineer and figure out why
they went viral. All right? And then
it'll use that same style and format to
basically create new tweets, new posts
based off of the info that Ben gave you,
the knowledge that he has experienced,
right? So that way you create um posts
yourself.
So here's an example of a tweet that
generated by cloud. And then you know
you obviously you can create hundreds of
these posts per day,
right? Um and also you want to use this
script to clo basically like you want to
include as many numbers or stats because
you know um the more you do the more
interesting it becomes the more specific
the more real and you want to include
case studies, examples, stories. Uh all
of this stuff is basically just to help
um it create posts that are more
interesting and more likely to go viral.
So if you post this then it'll work
great. All right. So cloud templates uh
once you use all this you should start
going viral. You know obviously don't
expect to get lots of views go viral
within your first post but um you know
the nice thing is that you can create
hundreds or thousands of posts um very
easily. And uh you know the more you
post the more you learn the more you
learn from your mistakes and the more
chance of you have succeeding later on
like cuz again I made probably like
hundreds of posts more than like 900
posts before I had my first viral post
on Twitter. So it's a similar to similar
thing for you like I don't I don't want
you guys to create that many posts. Like
I expect you guys to you know do a lot
less because I had no idea what I was
doing back then. But, you know, now that
I'm giving you the blueprint and how to
do it, it should be a lot easier. Um,
so, you know, basically start getting
lots of views, making lots of posts. All
right. So, the thing about Twitter is
that you don't need a lot of views. You
don't need a lot compared to like
Instagram, YouTube, uh, Tik Tok, you're
like you're getting millions of views.
Like Twitter, you don't need a lot of
views. even just like 50,000 views here,
you know, um
49,000 views in a single post. It's not
a lot, but for Twitter, it's pretty
good. 448 comments. This post got 448,
right? Each person, each and every
single person who commented on this post
got a free ebook. They got a they got a
free guide. basically like as soon as
you comment on this post, you instantly
get a DM basically saying, "Oh, here's
my guide." You know, you can read it for
free. So, people are getting stuff for
free. So, that's why um you know, a lot
of people comment on it because uh
basically it costs nothing except maybe
like two seconds of your time and just
like type one word to receive the free
ebook that you can learn from, right?
And as you're getting more comments, as
you get hundreds of comments, the more
Twitter will u push it out to more
people. So, um you know, this is called
engagement farming. Basically, the more
comments it has, it basically tricks the
algorithm into thinking that the post is
popular. So, it pushes out to 49,000
people to view.
All right. And let's generally like 50%
of them 50% of the people actually do
open the DM and check out the the guide,
right?
So by that logic if 400 people commented
then in that case 200 people would have
opened and read it and let's say 3% of
them buy the course for $300 each. Um 3%
is you know normal um $300 course is
what we're selling here and um you know
we get six sales from this from this one
post
for a total of $1,800. So, you know,
that's the thing about these kinds of
posts is that you can really look over
these posts. Like, it seems like you're
not making any it seems like they're not
making much money cuz it's only 49,000
views, but in reality, if you dig like
deeper, you'll figure out that, you
know, these posts are making a shitload
of money. All right? And then again, you
know, back to the partnership from
earlier. Um, you want to split the money
50/50 with your partner. So, if that
earlier post got $1,800, then you want
to split it in half. So, you get $900,
for example. And that's from one post,
which is pretty good, right? $900
screenshot. All right. So, again, why do
you want to split? Because you made the
post, you did the work, you created the
funnel, right? And the partner uh gave
you the knowledge and the authority. you
know, without the partner, you would not
been able to make posts that were um you
know, full [snorts] of value with his
knowledge and experience and authority.
Um like you'd only be able to make uh
very vague uh non-helpful general like
posts about AI for example, right? Um
and the partner is also delivering the
product or service to the customer. So
he's taking care of that. you don't need
to um you don't need to uh you know pay
attention to the fulfillment cuz he's
doing that for you, you know, but you're
making the post, you're getting the
views for him, you're driving the
traffic for him. So basically, that's
why you're splitting 50/50. All right?
And once you start your partnership, you
know, you can be very flexible, right?
You can you can be the one creating the
ebook. You can, you know, you can be
flexible and negotiate, you know, who
does what and then negotiate the split
as well. All right. So, [snorts]
um this is a oneweek stat. Um so you can
see November 3 to 9, that's basically 7
days. Within this one week, um with this
partnership, um basically a student made
$8,800.
Um you know, obviously there are fees,
right? Um these payment processors
collect a stupid amount of fees. So
after fees is $8,200.
Um, but you know, they're selling
basically uh I forgot whether it was
like a course or ebook. Basically, the
same thing. $700 and one $2,500 sale,
right? Okay. So, this is, you know,
basically what one of the students
achieved within one week. Um,
and so once you do the split, you know,
once you divide the $8,200 in half, you
get, you know, $4,100.
And so that's pretty good. That's pretty
good for, you know, one week of work. um
you know obviously the partner gets the
other half.
All right. So the next step uh you guys
need to use Tweet Hunter. Tweet Hunter
uh I'm going to basically for you for
you guys that are new uh why do you need
it? So [snorts]
the first thing is that it allows you to
do the autodm. Remember how I was
talking about the autodm earlier, right?
uh you can autodm which means that for
example if anyone likes or comments or
engages on your post it'll automatically
send out a DM and you can customize the
DM you can write whatever you want in
the DM to everyone so let's say you get
450 comments on one post that you made
right and then Tweet Hunter will
automatically send those DMs to everyone
hence auto DM right maybe you want to
sell uh like a ebook for $50 so you send
out like a checkout page should buy the,
you know, ebook. Or maybe you want to
sell like a more expensive, you know,
$1,000 course. Um, but you know, you
know that people aren't going to buy
immediately, so you want to warm people
up, you know, make them watch more
videos, uh, give them freebies to do
that. You can give them free training.
You can send that to them. Or you can
send a free, you know, you can send a
checkout link to buy an ebook or
something. You can buy, you can send
whatever you want. All right? So, it's
not manual. you don't have to reply to
people. Um, Tweet Hunter will just take
care of the uh DMs for you. It'll, you
know, DM everyone uh instantly.
All right. So, here's what it looks
like. Um, left is what you'll see on
Tweet Hunter. So, whenever someone
replies,
um, it will send this. In this case, I'm
sending people's uh like a like a
training. So like just free resources um
free courses, free videos, free
trainings and the reason why I do that
is because you know the more I give out
people well you know I want to basically
how have them understand right and uh if
they also learn they'll increase um you
know they'll trust you more right and
that allows you to have a higher chance
of selling something that's high ticket.
So you can see this is in my DMs. This
is my accounts. This is my DMs. It's
sending this messages message to
literally everyone who engages with my
post. So anyone who replies to the post
gets the autodm. So I hope that's clear.
And um you know it's sending thousands
of these DMs every single day. So even
if only like 0.5% or 0.2% 2% of people
end up buying is still a lot especially
if each sale is like 2,000 or $5,000,
right? Okay. So, the second reason why
you want to use Tweet Hunter is so that
you can schedule post in advance. So,
chances are you don't want to, you know,
make posts every single day. You don't
want to uh work on that. You want to be
efficient and uh, you know, create lots
of posts today and then for the rest of
the month, you don't want to worry about
it ever again, right? It's all taken
care of. So, let's say right now you
generate 900 tweets. You create 900
tweets, right? So, for the next 30 days,
you're going to make 30 tweets per day.
You know, this is hypothetical. Uh I
probably wouldn't make that many posts.
Um but, you know, as long as they're
high quality, um
you can make whatever post you want.
Again, like the number of tweets that
you don't that you make doesn't matter
too much. Um but it's more about the
quality. So, for example, if you have
900 tweets, you can split that up to 30
days, 30 tweets per day. Um, and then
they'll automatically be posted. So,
this is just an example, right? So,
you're doing all the work today and for
the rest of the month, you don't need to
worry about it. And the thing is that
um, you know, you don't need every
single post to get lots of views. Even
if only like 5% of your posts go viral.
Like, that's already huge, right? 5% of
900. What is that? That's like um 45
posts. Let's say that they're making
like 50,000 views each. You know, that's
quite a lot just for the amount of work
that you're putting right now.
All right. So, the entire system to this
business is all automated. So, you know,
back from that example of making um of
doing 900 posts. Um wait, give me a sec.
Yeah. So, um,
a bunch of you guys asked questions. Um,
so one thing is, you know, obviously you
don't want to post fake stuff. You want
to post things that are only real. You
don't want to lie. You want to, you
know, that's why you're partnering with
the partner because let's say the
partner made $3 million per year. Then
you can finally say that I made $3
million and this is how I did or not I
but how we did, right? because you're
work you're working together with him.
So, uh you want to create social proof
that's real and then if it's real,
people start believing you. You don't
want to create these fake stuff. That's
why you want to partner with these
people so that you can actually say uh
these things, you know, um if you
partner with someone who made $3 million
per year with AI, you can say, "We made
$3 million per year with AI. This is how
we did it." Um and give details that are
real that actually happened. Um so that
you know people benefit a lot from that.
So that's why um and again if you want
to find these partners just DM me just
just ask me just text me and I will give
you one. You know these people want
extra money as well. Um and you know
they're all very happy to work with you
guys. Um
so yeah uh that's
okay. So, you know, this entire thing is
completely automated. So, you're making
uh lots of posts. Um you spend time
doing that and then you're taking care
of, you know, everything for the rest of
the month is automated, right? You don't
need to do marketing anymore. Uh you're
finished with all your work. Um and then
you're just automatically getting views,
you're getting engagement, comments,
followers, uh while you sleep, right?
You don't have to do anything. You don't
have to be on your phone. You don't have
to be working at all. You can be at your
job or whatever. And then even if only a
small percentage of your posts go viral,
you know, you're still getting lots of
views and followers, you don't need
every single post to get lots of views.
And then again, Tweet Hunter will um
automate the entire DM so that when
someone, you know, likes or comments on
your post, then they will automatically
receive a DM basically to like a freebie
or like a like a course or something and
they'll just buy, you know, they'll buy.
Um or maybe you know it's a it's a link
to book a call um and then you close
right and then you know in that case you
want to hire a closer. So basically what
a closer does is they convince the the
lead to buy something but in return they
take 10% of the sale. So let's say for
example I'm trying to sell like an AI
course right and I'm trying to sell that
for $3,000.
I don't have to get on the call with a
lead. the closer gets on the call with
the lead, convinces them to buy, right?
Um, of course, they won't convince
everyone to buy, but you know, good
amount of people they'll convince to buy
and they'll take 10% of it. So, they'll
take $300 of the $3,000 and then I keep
the rest of the $2,700. You keep the
rest, right? So, I hope that makes
sense. All right. So, all this is
automated once you build the entire
system.
So here is an example example case study
example post. So this post got 37,000
views. It's very simple, you know. It's
look at how stupidly simple this post
is. Takes like 10 seconds to write this
post and then you know you just attach a
few images and obviously working with a
partner here. So 159 comments this post
got. And I want you guys to guess how
much money we made from this one post.
From this one single post. Is it 500,
3,000, 10,000 or $20,000 or more? All
right. So, I want you guys to guess.
All right. So, in the meantime, I I'll
reveal this later. By the way, um I want
to show you guys basically how this
entire process works. So, you see the
post.
So, you know, we have the account and
then as soon as people uh comment on
this post,
you know, if you're one of the five 159
people that comments, you'll basically
get invited to a the free Discord where
there are lots of free ebooks to learn
from. You know, there's a lot of stuff
that you can learn and then
um you know, you basically learn how it
all works, right? It's free. And then um
at the very end of the discord uh
basically there's a form where people
can apply for uh co coaching. So
basically for those who are interested
in buying coaching, right? So I hope
that's simple. People uh the viewers
will see these posts and they'll comment
on it and they'll receive an a DM
automatically, right? And the DM will be
a link will contain a link to this
discord
and discord will contain a lot of free
material where people learn and they
become very interested like let's say I
join this discord and I read all this
stuff I'm like wow you know this is
great I want to learn more I want
coaching so you know if they want it
then they apply for uh this form they uh
fill out an application so from this one
account not not this one post but this
entire account from all the posts Total
from this account, we got 1,800
submissions for this application, people
who wanted uh the coaching, 1,800 people
applied. And then out of those 1,800
people, um again, this is, you know,
this lifetime from this from this uh
count. So over the or over the course of
many many posts that were made um 1,800
calls uh 577 calls were actually made
you know. So uh all these people apply
but we only did 577 calls and then uh
our conversion rate was pretty low. It's
like around 25%. So, we actually got 132
sales. 132 people bought it uh out of,
you know, 1,800 people who uh applied.
Um, in the average sale, average sale
was eight uh was $4,300.
So, the average person paid $4,300 for
the coaching and 132 people paid for
that. We made $570,000
cash collected.
All right. So basically, what did we
sell? What does what does this account
sell? You guys are probably wondering
that. What what do we sell? Oh yeah, by
the way, as a disclaimer, um basically
the partner was someone who was actually
successful uh with making money with AI
models. Um so the guy was actually
successful and we like I partner up with
him, right?
And then I'm basically making the posts
and he's the expert. He is the guy who
actually um is successful at this
business. So I partner with him and
together basically uh do make uh make
these uh sales right and of course he is
fulfilling um
the the the sales basically he's
fulfilling delivering all the stuff. So
how does it work? What do we sell on
this account and what do the clients
get? Basically, uh, a few things. So,
one, they're chucked into like a paid
Discord. So, remember where I showed you
the free Discord from earlier? Uh, they
get chucked into another Discord for 3
months, a paid version where there are
more materials. Um, you know, the
students can collaborate. Um, they can
mingle, they can do calls, you know,
they can help each other, they they can
do masterminds and stuff like that.
basically like um you know like a big
friend circle you know and then we give
them uh courses like modules so um
videos documents basically uh he is
teaching Parker is teaching people um
how to do this business right how to
grow it so basically it's purely
educational uh so that people can learn
and then implement those strategies into
you know building it and then they get
one-on-one coaching from Parker um the
students, you know, that became
successful, that actually started making
money with this business actually uh
became COVID coaches as well to help
Parker. And of course, there's a 7-day
guarantee. So, if anyone is not happy,
if anyone regrets, you know, buying this
for 4,300, and that's that's average, by
the way. So, it was originally $5,000,
but some people want a discount, so
that's why the average came down to
4,300. Um but you know if anyone was
dissatisfied or they regret making the
purchase or you know they're not happy
we just gave them a full refund if it
was within seven days right and
basically we made sure to uh give out as
much value as possible to people to help
people um really benefit all these
people right the people who bought so we
keep constantly updating u with new
material with new modules with new
learnings um just like how you know in
Hustler University and Andrew Tate's
course you know people like they keep
adding new things every week. That's why
it's so valuable and people keep paying
$50 per month. That's why people keep
paying, you know, every month. That's
why it remains valuable. So that's what
you want to do. Um so I hope that makes
sense. Basically exactly what we sold
and what the clients got and how uh the
funnel works, right?
So to go back to the question, this one
post, this one single post right here
that took maybe a few seconds to write,
maybe like, you know, 30 seconds to
write the text, you know, 20 seconds to
attach the images, it this post made us
$27,000, right? We got six sales of, you
know, almost $5,000 each from this one
post, $27,000,
right? So that's the thing about Twitter
is that people look at the number of
views and that's like oh wow that's
that's nothing right but then they don't
realize that the quality of the viewers
the audience is so high on Twitter
that's you know people have lots of
money and even just like one person
buying is a lot of money so these posts
are making a lot so that's why you know
over the course of this entire uh
account we made $570,000
um right now you know we've discontinued
I've discontinued because I'm like okay
I'm a
This is not good for me. This is a
business topic that I don't want to
continue with. So that's why we ended,
right? Okay. $570,000 within approximate
threemonth period. Um so you know
basically was splitting with with the
partner, 50% uh from me, 50% for him.
Each person gets like $285,000 almost
300k. So that's like you know almost
100k per month for each of us from just
one account, right? and I have many many
other accounts.
Okay. All right. And of course, this
works with any other niche. It doesn't
have to be AM models. It doesn't have to
be AI. It doesn't have to be YouTube. It
could be ecom. It could be um it could
be sales. It could be trading. Um it
could be any niche. And it works exactly
the same as long as you um make the
posts in the same format, the same
style. As long as you make posts that
are getting viral uh views um and you're
basically helping people uh uh giving
out free educational content and you go
through this exact same funnel and
you're selling, you know, digital any
digital product, you know, it works.
Like it doesn't have to be, you know,
this topic. You could be selling ebooks.
You could be selling a service. You
know, you could be selling a service
that basically helps them set up the
business. of course not guarantee
results, but you know, set up websites,
set up set up a bunch of stuff. Um, you
could sell coaching, you could sell
course, you could sell ebooks, you could
sell whatever you want, right? It's not
limited to just um like a like one
thing. And you can post about any topic.
It works completely fine. All right,
let's see if any of you guys have any
questions right now. Um, [clears throat]
oh no, not here.
Yep. Okay. So,
um, [clears throat]
so this is one of my students, Peter.
He's 18. I don't know if he's 18 still.
He might be 19 now. Um, but basically, I
made a video with him because he was one
of my students. And I was so excited
because he started making more than
$1,000 profit per day, you know. Um I'm
not really sure what his background is.
Um but you know he basically joined. Um
this picture on the bottom left is his
first sale that he made. He made his
$300 sale and then you know uh after
that he starts making so many more
sales. Um but you know you can go watch
a YouTube video on my channel if you'd
like. Basically uh where I helped him uh
get up to $1,000 plus profit days. Um,
you know, the quality of the video is
kind of bad because, you know, I I was
just it was my old MacBook and uh I was
so excited about creating this thing.
Um, basically it's unedited. It's all
authentic. Uh, it's completely um
it's completely authentic basically. Um,
so you can go watch it. It's basically
like an entire story from A to Z of how
we built everything. his complete story
and you know obviously running this
business building this business like
you're going to have a lot of um
troubles like problems that come up that
are unexpected how we address those how
we overcame um so every single detail of
of our progress that I made he shares in
that video so you can go watch I have
more of these kinds of videos by the way
so now like fast forward to a month that
was seven years seven months ago but now
like he's making a lot more um you know
I asked him recently this was
uh two weeks ago. I'm like, "How like,
how are you doing, bro?" And he's like,
"Bro,
we just did $250 $250,000 last month."
So, you know, the growth that they make,
it's it's actually crazy. And obviously,
you know, there are more uh videos on my
page. Um I hope it allows you to learn,
you know, allow allows you to learn um
that you get a lot of benefits out of
watching these videos. um it helps you
succeed. So um the more information that
you have, the more education um the more
chance and the faster that it takes for
you to succeed. So um you know the harsh
reality for me is that many of my
students, many of my mentees will
surpass me uh in performance. And you
know the the the thing is that um all of
us like me and like all these all these
people, they were just you know normal
people. They're just playing video games
in their mom's basement. and they're
just like, you know what I mean?
Basically, they were just normal kids
like just a few years ago and now, you
know, um they're becoming successful and
uh you know, I'm proud to say that a lot
of them will become some of the world's
leading entrepreneurs soon. So, you
know, let's revisit your dream life in
one year from earlier that we did a few
minutes ago. So, I'm wondering if you
can see yourself achieving those goals
now. And I'm wondering if you can see
yourself um using this bridge to achieve
those goals. Like do you see how you
will go from uh being where you at right
now to those goals in one year? And how
like what is the bridge that will take
you to there? Right? And I want I'm
wondering if you see this business
uh being that bridge to take you to
achieving those goals in one year.
Right? So I just want you to think about
that.
So let me show you a student who
actually did this exercise like you know
um what kind of goals you want in one
year, right? So this is a real example
um of a student who did this exercise
that I forced him to do this exercise.
I'm like okay think of yourself in one
year. What do you want? So this his name
is Zayn. Um he's one of my students. He
joined May 2025. So it's like I think
around 8 months ago or something like
that. Um okay. So I'm like what car are
you going to buy in one year? You know
he just joined. And I'm like what car
are you going to buy? All right. Once
you become successful and he's like okay
I want to buy a G Wagon. And he's like
okay I'll be happy even if I had a
Toyota. And so I asked him, you know, to
commit to that goal, to be 100% certain
that he'll achieve it, right? He's in
high school. Um he's working at a
part-time cafe. Uh he's working
part-time at a cafe. You know, you can
imagine he's barely earning anything. He
has almost no experience. He's tried
watching, you know, drop shipping
YouTube videos. Um but, you know,
basically had no success. So this is a
student that, you know, I took on last
year. And then you know basically a few
months later I think this was uh
what basically less than a year he does
achieve it. He gets he buys a Gwagon
right he gets these results and you know
he uh writes this long testimonial. I
mean I kind of asked him to write the
testimonial just because I you know um
he told me that he would once he become
successful. So here's the pictures of
the G Wagon he bought. you know, it was
$57,000 paid in cash. It's an older used
one, so that's why it's, you know, it's
cheaper than normal, but, you know,
still it's it's a huge accomplishment.
So, I was very proud of that. That's a
real life example of this one year um
exercise, you know, being fulfilled. So,
you know, he does 100, he's doing now
crazy amounts per month. And uh you know
here are some of his dashboards and you
can talk to him if you'd like on
telegram. This is a link you can talk to
him. Um and uh basically
the the reality is that you can achieve
your dream of life in one year, right?
Just like how that student did.
But there are three requirements.
Three. So one is that you need to know
your goals very clearly.
Um and you actually already did this
step earlier. You know you basically
wrote thought of your goals. Number two
is that you need to believe that you'll
achieve all of these goals with 100%
certainty with every fiber in your body
with every cell in your body. You need
to believe that that it's inevitable
that failure is impossible. You need to
believe this. Right? So once you do
that, you're you're done with step two.
You know, you just need these three
steps to basically accomplish this 100%.
Number three is that you need to put in
the work, the steps to make it work. So,
you know, to make posts, to use the AI,
to create the products, to talk to
clients, you know, do this work daily.
You don't have to, you know, put in a
lot of work today, but as long as you're
making steps, right? It's similar to,
you know, climbing Mount Everest. Maybe
you're at bottom right now. you don't
need to take a lot of steps right now,
but as long as you keep think making
steps and eventually you'll be surprised
how much progress you make. Uh you know
you'll be quite high in the mountain and
eventually you'll reach the top. So it's
very similar to business. You know you
just continue to put in the work, put in
the right steps, right? Follow the
blueprint and then you'll succeed. So
this is Michael Michael's story. So I
think he reached he reached out to me
April of last year. So that was 10
months ago. You can see here that he's
messaging me a lot. Um, you know, I get
thousands of messages every week, so
it's difficult for me to reply, but I
finally responded like, "Hey, what's
up?" And then I basically decide to help
him succeed with this business, you
know, because I can see his hunger in
his in his um words. I guess I I I can't
see him. So, like I can feel the energy,
the hunger that he has to succeed. So,
that's why I take him on. Um
and then you know
obviously he's making a lot of these
posts and he's not getting views but
eventually he does get views and you
know he gets views on X he also gets
views on Tik Toks you know so the same
concept applies to any platform you know
you're basically making valuable content
that's educational that grabs people's
attention that uh captures someone
emotionally right um basically the whole
concept is the same even though if it's
in different formats videos for text uh
Tik Tok or X you know basically um once
you understand how to get views um you
can use it to wherever you want so you
know he's getting lots of views on X and
also Tik Tok you know so this is Tik Tok
129,000 views on one post so he's making
you know a lot of these posts um I'm I'm
actually reading this because I forgot
what uh we we mentioned in the posts in
the in the Telegram chats
Okay. So, basically like, you know, I
asked him when was this, how do you make
the post, how many comments, how many
leads he got. So, you know, this was a
screenshot, right? He's selling an ebook
or course for $300 to $800 each. So, you
know, each sale is a lot. Um, and he has
these videos. He has more of these
videos, many, many more, and also many
more, you know, Twitter posts. Um, and
then he's getting lots of sales, right?
So he mentions how he got approximately
50 sales in a very short period of time
selling these things. Um and you know
that's pretty successful. That's that's
great, right? Um and now he's a coach.
Uh so that's one thing that I do with my
students is that when they become
successful, I basically invite them to
become co- coaches for me. So obviously,
you know, I'm teaching my students. Uh
but if my students become successful, I
take the successful successful students
and have them teach the students, right?
if that makes sense. Similar to you know
let's say um you have a math teacher in
class and then you have a lot of
students but then like one student is
genius so that you know he joins the
teacher and starts teaching the class.
So it's basically the same concept. Um
so basically you know he's Michael for
example he's um teaching he's helping me
teach all these students. So in each of
these group chants you can see uh these
are each group chants A M like these are
each group chance uh for each student.
So um Michael and I we're basically you
know there are two coaches for every
student. Um so we're really helping
these people out. We're we're hopping on
calls to help the students and all that
stuff. Um so [clears throat] basically
like I'm inviting you guys to join my
pyramid scheme right obviously it's a
joke but um basically once you become
successful
um you can join me to become a coach and
we can help even more students become
successful 10 pyramid scheme but
obviously this is a joke um it's an
infinite positive loop right so that's
why I'm inviting you guys um basically
if you're thinking if you're interested
in starting online business, right? And
you just don't know how. You just don't
know what like the blueprint of how to
do that. And um you want someone to help
you. Um obviously it's not going to be
easy at all. Um it's going to be like
Olympic training because like becoming
successful business is always difficult.
There's no such thing as an easy
business that's to succeed with, right?
Um so basically like uh we're going to
help you. These successful students of
mine and me, we're all going to help
you. It's not going to be easy. Once
again, like it's going to be similar to
like an Olympic training, Olympic coach.
You know, you can't expect to go to show
up every day thinking it's going to be
easy. We're going to demand a lot of
you. Um, we're going to expect you to
work hard, right? We're going to push
you. We're going to keep you
accountable. Um, but that's all for the
reason because we want to make you as
successful as possible, right? And so,
if you want to join, there are some
requirements. There are some um things
that we ask you of. Obviously, if
Olympic coach is going to take on new
people to teach or to guide, like
they're not going to take everyone,
right? They're going to filter down to
uh small number of people. So, our
requirements is that you're going to
need to like basically be hugely
committed, have a huge work ethic,
long-term vision, not just treat this as
a side hustle or side gig, but you know,
to treat this as a long-term business,
to be very committed to this, spend 10
hours per week. um you know, be
consistent. Don't just like put in a few
hours of work in a week and just like
not show up anymore, right? You want to
be consistent. Um and we're expecting
you to, you know, work hard and to, you
know, basically achieve success, you
know, we're expecting you to um within 3
months basically start making money, you
know, and if you're not um if we don't
see the potential in you, then we're not
going to accept you inside, you know.
We're very selective. Um and uh you know
the nice part is that basically if
you're accepted um we want you to
achieve 10K in three months or you don't
pay you know I think that's fair right
um and we're we're very confident about
that. So the reason why I'm doing this
like what's the benefit for me right why
am I doing this am I selling a course am
I making money off of this and yes I am
yes I am but uh the main thing the main
thing is that uh I take I basically get
an equity uh in each person in each
student right so I take 20% stake so
this um for example you make $10,000 in
a month I take 2k of that and then you
know uh for example if 30 students of
mine are making $10,000 a month each.
That's $300,000 total, right? And I'm
making $60,000 per month passively
because of that 20%, right? So, you're
sharing 20% of your profits with me. Uh,
so I I help you succeed, but in
exchange, you basically um what is it?
You share with me the profits. And this
is not indefinite. This is just the
first year. And the more you succeed,
the more I benefit, obviously, because
the more money you make, the more uh I
make from that split, right? So that's
why I want you to succeed. And so here
is an example of a chart uh from
December. These were the top some of my
top five students. This is top student,
you know, number two, number three,
number four, number five students. And
this is my equity in each student. So
20% 20%. This is normal. Uh this this
student basically we negotiated down to
5%. Um and this was my split out of you
know their earnings. And so you know
this I basically mark if I received it
or not and basically how I received it
right. So you can see here that just
from teaching these students I made
$50,000 per month for myself right in
December. Okay. So
here is the game plan. If you're
interested in joining I have this form
this onboarding form. You just put in a
few like you know details about
yourself. your name, um your email, your
phone number, and a few other
information. And then basically, uh I'm
going to hop on a call with you, like
not a closer or setter, but like
actually me, like one-on-one. Uh
basically to um you know, customize a
game plan for you, like tailor to you,
custom to you, right? Based off your
background, your experience, all that
sort of stuff. Um we're I'm going to
create for you a game plan to achieve
your goals uh you know a lot faster than
you could possibly do by yourself.
So uh let me share that with you guys um
in the chat so that you have access to
that.
Um oh this is super inconvenient. I
should have done this. Um, somehow
but yeah, so I'll put in the chat here
you guys can access. I'll also put it in
Telegram. Okay, never mind. Um,
yep. So, I hope you guys have access to
that. Host and panelist everyone. There
we go. Okay. So, apply here.
All right.
So
[clears throat] yeah, back to
uh the the master class. So um hopefully
you guys can still see my screen. I
don't think you can. Um
yeah, let me share my screen again.
Okay, sure. Okay. So again, uh once you
fill out that link, once you go to the
link, fill out the form and then you'll
be able to hop on a call with me and
I'll put together a custom game plan for
you like a like a strategy uh that you
can achieve um success in this business.
So like you know like a timeline of what
you'll be doing um at each stage of this
business so that you can achieve
success. All right. So, um I also offer
like a done for you basically where uh
instead of just a mentorship, this is
like a premium on top of the mentorship.
It's a superior premium version.
Basically, I'll build you I'll build for
you a Twitter account uh that's
generating lots of views and getting
substantial sales, right, within three
months. That's why it's called done for
you because I'm doing it for you, right?
Uh you get to choose the niche or topic.
It can be AI, it could be ecom, uh ecom,
you can be YouTube, it can be whatever
you want, right?
And then uh I will basically grow that X
account and um yeah grow that X account
and um
yeah so for example let's say that I
make a X account for you about YouTube
and we're selling ebooks, right? So
basically I'm making a lot of posts for
you about YouTube and we're selling
ebooks. So I'll set up everything for
you [snorts] from A to Z. So, all you
have to do is basically just, you know,
uh keep an eye out on any updates that I
may have uh for you guys. Um and I'm so
confident that if if we're not
successful in 90 days, just get a
complete refund. So, that's something
else that I offer. All right. So, you
know, here's another student that was
basically successful. He's high school.
Um you know, no business experience
whatsoever. Uh
this is how we started basically. He
just like reaches out to me like, "Yo,
what's what's good?" And then I'm like,
"Okay, I'll help you out." All right.
But the thing about him is that he was
just so pessimistic, so negative. He's
like, "I want to work hard, but like I
don't know if promoting this will be,
you know, will get me to where I want to
be." I'm like, "Bro, you need to like
change your mindset and like believe
that it's actually possible. If you're
so negative, you won't you're not going
to achieve success, right?" Um and then
you know basically I'm telling him to
you know stop being so scared and
actually you know uh put those emotions
aside and to actually believe and have
confidence in himself and you know put
in the work you know uh keep telling him
and then you know we start making posts
right we start making posts we choose AI
as the topic to write about um and then
he also creates this ebook he creates
this ebook 250 59 pages. Uh he creates
it with AI obviously. Um and this ebook
is actually teaching people how to use
AI to automate their business. Um so
basically it's really helpful for the
business owners and we're actually
genuinely helping this business owners
to like um systematize and make their
business more efficient um make making
their um operations making their systems
uh more efficient. So basically it's
kind of like a course um like an it's an
ebook course. It's a course inside an
ebook course in an ebook format. And
we're charging basically $1,000 per
copy, right? [clears throat] $1,000 per
copy of this.
And you know, he also sets up um the
Loom. He also sets up his Telegram.
So, you know, we start making these
sales. You know, we have this ebook
selling for $1,000. We start making
these sales. I mean, he does. He does.
I'm not doing it. He does. Um so, that's
his first sale. 1,000 bucks. Um [__]
notification. And obviously we hide the
name for privacy of the customer. Um
this is his um first sale first day
sales dashboard. Uh $1,700, right? First
day as a 17-year-old. That's huge. And
then he's sending me these screenshots.
He's like, "Wow, that's that's a lot."
So basically the funnel is like, you
know, X to Telegram. um where people
will basically DM him and then he will
you know the the leads the customers
will ask questions about you know this
this ebook and then people buy. So these
business owners uh who are interested in
integrating AI into the business are
coming to him. You know, his name is
also Alex, just as a reminder. They're
coming to Alex. Um and uh they're buying
his ebook, this ebook for a,000,000
bucks each. And you know, he's 17, so he
doesn't have like he's not able to
create a like a payment processor for
himself. So I have to do that for him. I
have to create a banking uh system for
him and then like basically share access
with him. So that's, you know, we're
doing the profit split there, right? So
more more sales, more screenshots. He
starts to continuously do, you know,
four figures per day in profit. You
know, $1,000, $1,700 first day, right?
And then, yeah, just more sales, you
become successful. And um, you know,
there are hundreds of other successful
students that I have. So here's a
promise that I make for you guys. You
know, once you get to your first
$10,000, that's why it's called $10,000
promise, $10,000, I c I invite you here
to LA to Los Angeles, and then I'll
invite you to the tallest restaurant
here to come celebrate. You know, these
this is that's me with my students to
come celebrate with me once you hit
$10,000. And then we'll discuss how to
um scale beyond that. Yeah. Um,
obviously we're going to have a very
good time, you know, talking, you know,
celebrating, but then we're going to
strategize how to go beyond that
and then we're going to basically you
can you can choose a car. You can choose
any exotic car like Ferrari,
Rolls-Royce, Lamborghini. Um, and then
we'll go around with that. Right? So,
that's a $10,000 promise that I have for
you guys.
So yeah, if you're interested uh either
the done for you or the mentorship, then
you can go ahead and fill out that form.
Basically, once you filled that out,
I'll be hoping on a one-toone call with
you. Be I'll be on the call with you,
just onetoone, and I'll create a custom
game plan for you so that you can
succeed. Um, and this is available until
February 24, um, midnight PSTs, and it's
also 20% off now. So, um, if you're
interested, even if you're like slightly
interested, uh, you can fill out the
form. Um, and I'll send you more details
later once you do fill that out. Um, and
then, you know, if you're, if it's a
good opportunity for you, then that's
great. But if not, you know, that's
fine, too. Um, it's basically wherever I
can help you out most. Um, I want you to
choose whatever you think is best for
yourself, whatever opportunity is best
for yourself after, you know,
understanding um, completely. Um, and
then you can choose for yourself and
then you know if I can help like I'll be
an honor to basically help you out here.
So that's basically it for the master
class. I hope this has been helpful. Um,
if you have any more questions uh please
do reach out to me on XDM or Telegram or
you know you can text me as well. Um,
and then once you fill out the form um
you should be able to we'll hop on a
call basically to go over the next
steps. So um yeah, that's pretty much
it. I hope you guys um you know learned
a lot from this master class. That was
the goal. The primary goal was really to
uh help you guys to learn um even just
the basics. I hope it's been helpful and
uh you know if you have again if you
have any other questions just feel free
to reach out to me. I'm happy to help in
whatever way. I'm happy to answer any
questions. Um, so we had a